daytime sky [music] using acrylic
marker.  Hi guys, this time I'm using
Miracle Works.  [music] This one has 60
colors.  The tip is dual tip, consisting
of a brush and felt tip pen.  After
making the sun, I sketched it first
using a pencil.  Then I filled it with
blue [music] color.  Well, if you want to use
acrylic markers, you have to be quick, because in
less than 3 seconds [music] they'll
dry.  For the bottom clouds
we mix blue, [music] lime
green and yellow.  And the yellow color
is at the top.  The rest we can use
purple, light purple, mouth,
then pink, and salmon [music] pink.
Don't forget to color the middle part with
lemon yellow and yellow.  Repeat for
all the empty sections.  Don't forget to
blend or tap immediately before it
dries.  You can also add white cloud decorations
[music]
between the two blue clouds.  Well,
we just need to add a white [music] line and a
white dot in the cloud.  And here is the
result.  Don't forget to tek nala if
you succeed.  Ah.